

# **MUZAFFAR MUNIR**

# Software Engineer

## **PROFILE**

I am a professional software engineer having excellent expertise in diverse technologies & have done numerous projects including ERP and want to join a where there is healthy growth and a competitive environment in which I will be able to participate in learning and improve my existing professional skills as well as learn new technologies.

# CONTACT

#### **Email**

muzafarmunir@gmail.com

#### Phone

+923406168990

#### Website

https://muzaffarmunir.github.io/muzaffarmunirportfolio

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muzaffar-munir-300060110

## **SKILLS**

Angular

Vue js

Laravel

Node js

Git

NoSQL

Relation DB's

Rest Apis

Server Deployments(Cpanel, linux, fileZilla)

# **EDUCATION**

## BS IT(information technology), University of Gujrat, Gujrat Pakistan

Aug 2014 - Aug 2018

I have done my Bachelor's (BS) in Information technology from the University of Gujrat(UOG) Gujrat. During my graduation, I gained a lot of experience and learn new skills along the way. Always ready to try new things and expand my horizons.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Engineer, Virtual Force Inc., Lahore

Nov 2021

Working as a team member and have the following main responsibilities:

- Identify requirements from existing applications developed in Angular js
- Development of those requirements in Angular latest version
- write down modules, components, and services for API integration in Angular

## Software Enginner, I3RL pvt Ltd, Lahore

Feb 2021 - Nov 2021

Working as a team member and have the following main responsibilities:

- Identify requirements from the existing application
- Development of those requirements in Angular
- write down modules, components, and services for API integration in Angular

## Sotrware Engineer, OptimaGeeks, Lahore

Nov 2018 - Jan 2021

Working as a team member and have the following main responsibilities:

- Development of New Modules
- Defining API specifications and Database Design
- Development of the API with Node js using express js, Laravel & Yii2
- API Integration With Vuejs, Angular.
- Debug software components identify and fix as per requirements
- Upload and config domains on servers in AWS and Digital Ocean